glamzilla.com 2009-10-13

# Privacy Policy | glamzilla

**Glamzilla Privacy Policy**  
The following privacy statement covers Glamzilla website. Please read this statement regarding our website. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.glamzilla.com/contact/).

**Ownership of Information**  
Glamzilla is the sole owner of the information collected on the Glamzilla websites. 

**Comments**  
In order to enhance their use of the Glamzilla websites, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. To leave a comment, users must register. Glamzilla uses this system to screen out users who leave comments prohibited by our terms and conditions of use.

**Mailing List**  
Glamzilla may launch a mailing list for Glamzilla website. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a site’s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site, including new articles added to the site as well as emails from third party site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

**Public Forums  
**This site makes chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, Glamzilla has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Glamzilla only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Third Party Advertising**  
Glamzilla use third-party advertising companies including Google, among others, to serve ads when you visit our websites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Log Files**  
Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Glamzilla may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of the Glamzilla websites.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event Glamzilla goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Links**  
The Glamzilla websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Glamzilla is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Glamzilla.

**Notification of Changes**  
Whenever Glamzilla changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.glamzilla.com/contact/).
